Gage Norton

Phone: (612) 443 5008 | Email: nortongage0@gmail.com | Saint Paul, MN, USA

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gage-norton-a3568725b/

GitHub: https://github.com/Gatewayss

Summary

Through my experiences, I have developed a passion for problem-solving and thrive in collaborative environments. My father, who worked as a union rep for 15 years, instilled in me the importance of teamwork and effective communication to achieve common goals. I have witnessed firsthand how this mindset can lead to successful outcomes.

Work Experience

Kitchen Shift Lead - Can Can Wonderland

Saint Paul, MN May 2022 - Present

- Conducted pre-shift meetings to communicate goals, priorities and expectations.
- Demonstrated strong organizational skills, ensuring the product was consistent and the service was efficient.
- Provided coaching, training, and feedback to kitchen staff, promoting growth and development

Bartender - Alamo Drafthouse Cinema

Woodbury, MN December 2019 - May 2022

- Communicating with customers and the team to produce the best possible experience.
- Prioritizing a culture of teamwork and collaboration, often providing assistance to

other team members as needed.

Bartender - Buffalo Wild Wings

Saint Paul, MN January 2021 - June 2021

- Quickly resolved issues, requiring use of problem solving skills to ensure all quests were satisfied.
- Managed inventory and ordering supplies to ensure a successful business day.

Education

Full-Stack Web Development Certification (Coding Bootcamp)

University of Minnesota - Minneapolis, MN November 2022 - May 2023

Associates in Arts (AA)

Inver Hills Community College - Inver Grove Heights, MN August 2017 - May 2019

High school Diploma

Simley High School - Inver Grove Heights, MN August 2013 - May 2017

Skills

- · Web Development
- MySQL
- · CSS
- Git
- JavaScript
- · HTML5
- · APIs
- · REST
- Web Design
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

- GitHub
- SQL
- Node.js
- React
- GraphQL
- Back-end development
- Front-end development
- Bootstrap
- AWS
- ·JSON
- MongoDB
- jQuery